giftevery1.com 2012-06-17

# Privacy Policy

Giftevery1.com takes privacy seriously. The following statement reveals what you can expect from us regarding any personal data that you share with the site, and your rights and responsibilities associated with it. 

At Giftevery1.com, we understand the importance of protecting the confidentiality of information and other personal data provided by our clients. The protection of your privacy is kept in mind while designing and operating our system, and we make every effort to safeguard the patients’ data in accordance with all applicable legal requirements.

This statement describes our work arrangement, discussing how we acquire and use your personal information, and our policies and practices for keeping it secure. The users are urged to read this policy carefully and to periodically check for revisions. The date at the top of the page indicates the latest update of the policy.

We utilize [Secure Socket Layer (SSL) 128-bit encryption, firewalls and intrusion detection systems to keep your data safe. Only authorized employees are permitted to access the information provided by the clients and they are not allowed to use that data for any thong other than authorized business purposes].

Our security methods are effective and reliable, but no system is completely impassable, so we cannot guarantee that your information in our system is absolutely shielded. Also, we cannot guarantee that the information provided by you will not be intercepted as it is transmitted over the internet. Giftevery1 has several links to other websites. By providing such links we do not intend to endorse or promote their products/services. Also, we hold no responsibility of the content or information provided on these sites and are not accountable for their privacy practices. Clients are recommended to review the privacy statements posted on these sites before using or disclosing any personal information.

Giftevery1 does not record or track user visits; the information about the identity of our clients and their visits to our website are not recorded. A small file called “session cookie” is sometimes written on the user’s computer, and it expires when the user leaves the website. The information retained by session cookies only lasts during the session or for completing a particular online transaction; these cannot track users as they visit different sites over time.

We do not collect or use information about children under the age of 18 years, without the consent of their parents. Any information that we identify as belonging to a child under 18 will only be used to inform him/her that we will require parental consent before offering any help.

Any concerns or questions regarding the privacy practice at Giftevery1 can be e-mailed to info@ Giftevery1.com
